[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 [TENSE]😬 I can't believe our first day
at MIT. MJ, come on, pretend
[MUSIC/ambient]🎵 [ANGRY]😠 like you're not the happiest
you've ever been in your entire life.
[SAD]😢 I can't. I knew it. Hi, my name is Peter Parker.
You
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 don't remember me, but we used to know
each other. Something bad
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 was going to happen, and the only way to
stop it was
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 to make everyone forget about me.
Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
[TENSE]😬 I'm Spider -Man. Put your whimpering. Suit
yourself. Go home.
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 And sometimes Spider -Man has to do the
hard thing, even if
it breaks Peter Parker's heart. What is happening to me?
Excuse me,
[ANGRY]😠 Dr. Banner. I need your help. What did you say
your name
[LAUGHTER]😂 was? If DNA is mutating, it would be
enormously dangerous. Spiders have
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 three life cycles. When between cycles,
it can leave the spider vulnerable
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 to threats. We are faced with a danger
that we can't control.
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 One we can't even see. Stay out of my
way. You're losing
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 it, kid. And for those spiders who make
it through, it amounts
[LAUGHTER]😂 to a kind of keeper. Nice flowers. Oh,
they're a housewarming gift.
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 I'm MJ. I'm just a neighbor from across
the hall. Friendly neighbor.
[SAD]😢 The End.